{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Home Theater Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40308/":{"taskOID":40308,"originalTaskOID":40308,"setID":608,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":500101,"questionDisplayText":"Part of larger remodel","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this project part of a larger remodel?","shortQuestionText":"Part of larger remodel?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6337,"questionDisplayText":"System Components","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What components would you like for your new system?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20333,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Plasma or LCD TV","answerDisplayText":"Plasma or LCD TV","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20334,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Cable or Satellite TV","answerDisplayText":"Cable or Satellite TV","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20335,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"HDTV","answerDisplayText":"HDTV","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20336,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Xbox or Playstation","answerDisplayText":"Xbox or Playstation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20337,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"DVD Player","answerDisplayText":"DVD Player","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20338,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Projector \u0026 Screen","answerDisplayText":"Projector \u0026 Screen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20339,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Surround Sound System","answerDisplayText":"Surround Sound System","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20340,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Media Server","answerDisplayText":"Media Server","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20341,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"CD, Radio, or Cassette Player","answerDisplayText":"CD, Radio, or Cassette Player","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20342,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20343,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Universal Remote Control","answerDisplayText":"Universal Remote Control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501556,"questionDisplayText":"Already Purchased","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Have you already purchased the components for this project?","shortQuestionText":"Have you already purchased the components for this project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":202153,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - All","answerDisplayText":"Yes - All","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202154,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Yes - Some","answerDisplayText":"Yes - Some","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6338,"questionDisplayText":"Special features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What features are you interested in?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20344,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"In wall and ceiling speakers","answerDisplayText":"In wall and ceiling speakers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20345,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Multi-room or zone audio \u0026 video","answerDisplayText":"Multi-room or zone audio \u0026 video","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20346,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Home Theater Chairs or Furniture","answerDisplayText":"Home Theater Chairs or Furniture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20347,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Multi-level flooring","answerDisplayText":"Multi-level flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20348,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Custom lighting","answerDisplayText":"Custom lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20349,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"In wall touch screen controls","answerDisplayText":"In wall touch screen controls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20350,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"TV lifts or drop downs","answerDisplayText":"TV lifts or drop downs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20351,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Remote controlled blinds or shades","answerDisplayText":"Remote controlled blinds or shades","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6336,"questionDisplayText":"Electronic Preference","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes your preference in electronics?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20329,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Entry level","answerDisplayText":"Entry level","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20330,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"The best","answerDisplayText":"The best","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20331,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"High end","answerDisplayText":"High end","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20332,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Not sure","answerDisplayText":"Not sure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":500101,"questionDisplayText":"Part of larger remodel","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this project part of a larger remodel?","shortQuestionText":"Part of larger remodel?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6337,"questionDisplayText":"System Components","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What components would you like for your new system?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20333,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Plasma or LCD TV","answerDisplayText":"Plasma or LCD TV","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20334,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Cable or Satellite TV","answerDisplayText":"Cable or Satellite TV","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20335,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"HDTV","answerDisplayText":"HDTV","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20336,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Xbox or Playstation","answerDisplayText":"Xbox or Playstation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20337,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"DVD Player","answerDisplayText":"DVD Player","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20338,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Projector \u0026 Screen","answerDisplayText":"Projector \u0026 Screen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20339,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Surround Sound System","answerDisplayText":"Surround Sound System","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20340,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Media Server","answerDisplayText":"Media Server","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20341,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"CD, Radio, or Cassette Player","answerDisplayText":"CD, Radio, or Cassette Player","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20342,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20343,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Universal Remote Control","answerDisplayText":"Universal Remote Control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20333,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Plasma or LCD TV","answerDisplayText":"Plasma or LCD TV","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20334,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Cable or Satellite TV","answerDisplayText":"Cable or Satellite TV","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20335,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"HDTV","answerDisplayText":"HDTV","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20336,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Xbox or Playstation","answerDisplayText":"Xbox or Playstation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20337,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"DVD Player","answerDisplayText":"DVD Player","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20338,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Projector \u0026 Screen","answerDisplayText":"Projector \u0026 Screen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20339,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Surround Sound System","answerDisplayText":"Surround Sound System","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20340,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Media Server","answerDisplayText":"Media Server","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20341,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"CD, Radio, or Cassette Player","answerDisplayText":"CD, Radio, or Cassette Player","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20342,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20343,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Universal Remote Control","answerDisplayText":"Universal Remote Control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501556,"questionDisplayText":"Already Purchased","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Have you already purchased the components for this project?","shortQuestionText":"Have you already purchased the components for this project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":202153,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - All","answerDisplayText":"Yes - All","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202154,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Yes - Some","answerDisplayText":"Yes - Some","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":202153,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - All","answerDisplayText":"Yes - All","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202154,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Yes - Some","answerDisplayText":"Yes - Some","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6338,"questionDisplayText":"Special features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What features are you interested in?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20344,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"In wall and ceiling speakers","answerDisplayText":"In wall and ceiling speakers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20345,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Multi-room or zone audio \u0026 video","answerDisplayText":"Multi-room or zone audio \u0026 video","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20346,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Home Theater Chairs or Furniture","answerDisplayText":"Home Theater Chairs or Furniture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20347,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Multi-level flooring","answerDisplayText":"Multi-level flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20348,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Custom lighting","answerDisplayText":"Custom lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20349,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"In wall touch screen controls","answerDisplayText":"In wall touch screen controls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20350,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"TV lifts or drop downs","answerDisplayText":"TV lifts or drop downs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20351,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Remote controlled blinds or shades","answerDisplayText":"Remote controlled blinds or shades","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20344,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"In wall and ceiling speakers","answerDisplayText":"In wall and ceiling speakers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20345,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Multi-room or zone audio \u0026 video","answerDisplayText":"Multi-room or zone audio \u0026 video","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20346,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Home Theater Chairs or Furniture","answerDisplayText":"Home Theater Chairs or Furniture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20347,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Multi-level flooring","answerDisplayText":"Multi-level flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20348,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Custom lighting","answerDisplayText":"Custom lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20349,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"In wall touch screen controls","answerDisplayText":"In wall touch screen controls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20350,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"TV lifts or drop downs","answerDisplayText":"TV lifts or drop downs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20351,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Remote controlled blinds or shades","answerDisplayText":"Remote controlled blinds or shades","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6336,"questionDisplayText":"Electronic Preference","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes your preference in electronics?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20329,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Entry level","answerDisplayText":"Entry level","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20330,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"The best","answerDisplayText":"The best","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20331,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"High end","answerDisplayText":"High end","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20332,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Not sure","answerDisplayText":"Not sure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20329,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Entry level","answerDisplayText":"Entry level","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20330,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"The best","answerDisplayText":"The best","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20331,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"High end","answerDisplayText":"High end","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20332,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Not sure","answerDisplayText":"Not sure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/40308/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40308,"taskName":"Home Theater System or Media Center - Install","taskDescription":"Install or Replace a Home Theater System or Media Center","xmTaskDescriptor":"Home Theater Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":129,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"A/V Entertainment AV hook Media","textMessagingName":"Entertainment Sys","rolloverLongDesc":"Expert in linking together various components to achieve desired effects, enabling remote controls \u0026 other automated features. Note separate categories for servicing existing equipment \u0026 for installing full-blown home theater rooms.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes DVD, TV, VCR, home theater systems.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace a Home Theater System or Media Center.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Home Theater \u0026 Audio Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Surround Sound Systems","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":6,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Home Entertainment System Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Home Theater System or Media Center - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Home Theater Project","urlName":"Home-Theater-System-or-Media-Center-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Custom Home Theater System Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"A/V,Entertainment,AV,hook,Media,tv,projectorsaudio/visual,computer,audiovisual,visual,audio,Center,up,Theater,Systems,Equipment","emcCategoryOid":-12006,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":608,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}